One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Don't worry. I used the backs of my swords.
安心しろ　峰打ちだ
Why'd you have to knock out all the shipwrights?!
何で船大工全員のしちゃってんのよ！
Zoro's so strong!
ゾロは強えなあ！
Whatever, let's get going!
まあいいわ さっさと行くわよ！
Zoro, this way!
ゾロ　こっちだぞ！
Yup.
おう
No, this way!
いや！こっちだって！
You can't even follow us when we're leading the way?! You're a walking marvel!
先導してるのに どうやって間違えたの今！奇跡！
All right! I got out... since I'm rubber!
ああ～ 抜けられた！ゴムだから
Good job! Okay! Now remove mine!
やるな　よし！俺のを外せ！
Okay!
よしきた！
That bull and skull had better watch out!
見てろ… あの牛とガイコツ！
We've been undercover for five years.
我々が潜伏していたのは５年
Please don't worry. We took our cover jobs seriously.
ご安心を 仕事は全て手を抜かずにやりました
I understand your despair.
意気消沈お察しする
However, since we can't spend any more time on this matter,
しかし　我々がこの件に費やす時間も リミットを迎えましたので
we'll do whatever it takes to achieve our goal now.
目的遂行のため最善を尽くす気構え
Any resistance would be unwise; don't even think about it.
あまり考えのない抵抗ならば しないほうがよろしい
You've heard of "Cipher Pol," right?
サイファーポールという名をご存じのはず
People know them as CP1 through CP8.
俗に言うＣＰ１からＣＰ８まで
They're the World Government's top intelligence agencies, each with their own stronghold.
世界に８つの拠点を持つ 政府の優れた諜報機関
When the government orders it, they dig up any information from anywhere.
政府の指令で どんな場所のどんな情報でも探り出す
I've heard of them...
知ってるさ
but only up to CP8.
だがＣＰ８のことまでだ
Naturally.
そうでしょう
However, we are CP9, the ninth Cipher Pol, a supposedly nonexistent unit.
しかし我々はＣＰ９ 存在するはずのない９番目のサイファーポール
Since we possess a certain privilege, we can't operate publicly.
ある特権を持っているため 世の明るみには出られない
Privilege?
特権？
That's right.
そう…
In the name of justice to the very end,
あくまで正義の名の下にですが
when there are citizens who refuse to comply with the government...
我々は政府に対して非協力的な市民への
we are authorized to execute them.
殺しを許可されている
How self-serving! Murder in the name of justice is still murder!
身勝手な… 正義と名の付く殺しがあってたまるか！
The World Government has partially reconsidered the matter.
世界政府は一部考えを改めたのです
Rather than fearing the weapon's restoration,
兵器の復活を危惧し続けるよりも
they decided to awaken it to use as a force of justice that can end this Great Pirate Era.
いっそ兵器を呼び起こし この大海賊時代に終止符を打つ正義の勢力にしようと
However, you you don't want to help them do so.
しかしあなたはそれに協力しようとしない
As we speak, pirates are constantly victimizing people around the world,
今もなお　世界中で海賊たちから 被害を受け続けている人々を
yet you're saying you don't wish to save them.
あなたは救わないと言っているんだ
What nonsense... Restore that weapon, and the world will only fight over its power.
話にならん 兵器が復活すれば世界はその力を奪い合う
The cycle of destruction continues!
被害は拡大する一方だ
I get the sense you don't trust the government, Mr. Iceburg.
あなたは政府を信用していないようですね アイスバーグさん
I just know human nature, boy.
俺は人間の性を知ってるだけだ　小僧
Watch your tongue. I don't work for you anymore.
慎みたまえ いつまで上司のつもりでいる
Kaku, check his pulse.
カク　脈をとれ
Pardon me.
失礼
Mr. Iceburg, to tell you the truth, we developed a hypothesis a bit ago.
アイスバーグさん 実は先ほど我々に１つ仮説が生まれました
All you have to do is listen quietly while I explain it to you.
あなたはただ 私たちの仮説を黙って聞いていてくれればいい
I'm sure your blood will tell us the truth.
きっとあなたの血が真相を教えてくれます
Well then, allow me to elaborate on how we came to our hypothesis.
では　我々の仮説を 順を追って説明しましょう
First, we have doubts about your ploy of passing off the fake to us.
まず　我々に偽物をつかませるという あなたの行動　ここに疑問を感じる
You guessed that government officials were coming after the blueprints,
あなたは設計図を狙った犯人が 政府の人間だと推測して
so you hinted at where the fake was.
偽物の在りかを示した
However...
だが
if it was actually someone who was coming to kill you because of a grudge,
もしそうではなく　ただあなたに恨みを持った者たちが あなたを殺しに来ただけだった場合
the real blueprints would become abandoned, no longer passed down to a disciple.
本物の設計図は所有者を失い もはや伝承することができなくなってしまう
You're not stupid enough to overlook that possibility.
その可能性を考えないほどあなたはバカじゃない
Despite knowing that,
それを分かっていながらなお
you made no effort to transfer the real blueprints to anyone tonight.
今晩本物の設計図を 誰にも渡そうとしないということは
That means you've already entrusted them to someone.
実はもう誰かに託してある
At the very least, you don't have them with you.
少なくともあなたの手元にはもうない
That's what we believe.
そう考えられる
Give it a rest. No misbehaving.
無駄じゃ　暴れるな
This is still a hypothesis.
これはまだ可能性です
We haven't found any convincing proof of course.
もちろんどこにも確証はないし
Our surveillance and investigation over the past five years
この５年我々が監視調査した範囲でも
found no proof in your actions, either.
あなたの行動から取れる証拠もない
In addition, the person entrusted with the blueprints would need to be a proficient shipwright.
さらに　設計図を託される者には それにふさわしい船大工としての腕も必要
With that, I'll tell you the rest of our hypothesis.
さて仮説を続けましょう
This is where it gets interesting.
面白いのはこれからです
These are the fake blueprints that you passed off on us earlier.
先ほど 我々がつかまされた偽物の設計図
Look closely and you can see the signatures of the architects.
よく見ると 設計士のサインが入っているのですが
"Tom," "Iceburg," and "Cutty Flam."
トム　アイスバーグ　カティ･フラム
At the end, there's a company name: "Tom's Workers."
最後に社名　トムズワーカーズ
You might've thought that you outwitted your enemy by using these fakes.
あなたはこの偽物で敵を出し抜いた つもりでいたかもしれないが
But you never even dreamed that your enemy was hiding this close.
敵がこんなにも身近に 潜伏しているとは夢にも思わなかった
That was your miscalculation.
それが誤算
To a thief in the night who came after the blueprints,
ただ設計図を狙っただけの 昨日今日の侵入者にとっては
these would probably be worthless.
こんなものはただの紙くずでしょうが
But to us, who have lived in this city for the past five years,
ところが ５年間この町で暮らした我々には
these architects' names are very interesting.
この設計士の名前は興味深い
Mr. Iceburg, you have a guest.
アイスバーグさん　お客様が
Tom's Workers, led by the legendary shipwright Tom,
伝説の船大工トムの率いるトムズワーカーズは
was a shipbuilding company shrouded in mystery.
実に謎の多い造船会社
It seems to have once been on this island, but there's no payroll or company registration.
かつてこの島にあったはずだが 名簿も戸籍も存在しない
Just the fact that you were Tom's disciple was very difficult to dig up.
あなたがトムの弟子だということを 割り出すだけでも一苦労したものだ
According to the government's report, Tom had only two apprentices.
政府の報告によれば トムの弟子は２人しかおらず
And a government official confirmed that one died in an accident eight years ago.
１人は８年前の事故で死んだと 政府の人間がしっかりと確認している
Did you hear? Tom's violent apprentice, Cutty Flam, is dead.
知ってるかい？凶暴なトムの弟子 カティ･フラムは死んだんだそうだ
However, I remember hearing the name Cutty Flam before.
しかし　私はこの カティ･フラムという名を聞き覚えている
Mr. Iceburg, you have a guest. He said you would know him if I mentioned "Cutty Flam."
アイスバーグさん　お客様が “カティ･フラムと言えば分かる”と
It was about four years ago, shortly after we went undercover.
我々が潜入して間もなく… ４年ほど前のことです
There was a man who came through Galley-La Company's gate to see you.
ガレーラカンパニーの門をくぐり あなたを訪ねてきた男がいた
He used that name just once.
彼は一度だけその名を名乗った
I remember it, too.
私も覚えてます
Ditto.
わしもじゃ
Shall I show him in?
お通ししますか？
No. Turn him away.
いや　追い返せ
In other words...
つまり
Tom's other disciple Cutty Flam is still alive...
トムのもう１人の弟子 カティ･フラムは生きている
and lives in this town...
今もこの町で
after changing his name to Franky!
フランキーと名を変えて！
You've got a roundabout way of meeting people.
回りくどい会い方をするんだな
Aren't these the blueprints we saw for that ancient weapon?!
こりゃ…　何だよ 古代兵器の設計図じゃ…
Don't use the name Cutty Flam ever again.
この先カティ･フラムの名は捨てろ
Huh?
んあ？
It's only a matter of time before they come for me.
俺が狙われるのも時間の問題だ
Take them and leave the island, Franky.
そいつを持って島を出ろ　フランキー
It's plain as day.
間違いなさそうじゃな
I never would've guessed that you and that guy were connected like that.
まさか　あんたとあいつに そんなつながりがあったとは…
It's true that no matter how much we investigated Franky,
フランキーは確かに調べても調べても
we couldn't figure out his true identity.
素性の知れない男だったが
But we ignored him because he was just an ill-tempered ship dismantler.
解体屋であの横行ゆえ 鼻にもかけていなかった
Indeed... Since our speculation came entirely from the known facts,
なるほど 事実からしか生まれない我々の予測に
involving a "dead person" perfectly exploited our blind spot.
死人を関係させることは 絶好の死角
The Franky Family comes to the shipyard to sell lumber.
フランキー一家ならば 造船所へ材木を売りにやってくるし
So you had ample opportunity to arrange giving him the blueprints.
うまく申し合わせれば設計図を 受け渡すチャンスはいくらでもあった
Now, come to think of it, he was more like a neighbor who kept a safe distance.
改めて思えば 最も怪しまれない距離を保った隣人と言える
If you don't have the blueprints with you,
あなたの手元に設計図がないのなら
that you were able to hold firm makes sense.
さっきまでのあなたの強気な態度も納得
If you entrusted them to your fellow apprentice,
託した相手が あなたの唯一の弟弟子ならば
it stands to reason that you never gave them to any of the Galley-La foremen.
ガレーラの職長の誰にも託さなかったことも納得
After all this speculation, everything lines up.
これで予測は１本の線につながり
Furthermore...
さらに
your racing pulse proves everything!
あなたの波打つ血がそれを的中だと告げた！
Hurry!
急いで！
Hey!
おい！
Is this really the right way?
ホントにこっちでいいのか？
Not a word outta you!
あんたが言うな！
They're really hurt.
ひどいやられ方だ
Over there! That has to be the door!
あそこ！ あの正面の扉で間違いないわ
Lots of people are on the ground over there, too!
あそこにも いっぱい人が倒れてるぞ！
Huh?
えっ？お？
Right! Go on ahead of us, cut down the door, and rush in there!
さあ　前行きなさい　前！ 扉斬って突進よ！
– Go ahead!
–　どうぞ！
What the hell?! Don't order me around!
何だそりゃ！俺に命令すんな！
Hey, Straw Hat!
おい麦わら！
You idiot! Wrong room! It's the one next door!
バカ野郎　この部屋じゃねえ！ もう１つ隣の部屋だ！
Oh, it's the next one?
何だ　隣か
Well, it's not your fault.
なあに… あなたに罪はない
This has been a busy night.
これだけいろいろなことが起こる夜に
You're human, after all. It's only natural you couldn't hide your consternation.
動揺を隠せなくなるのは 血の通った人間ならば当然のこと
We appreciate what you've done for us, but we're through.
今日まで世話になりましたね あんたはもう用済みじゃ
Let's hurry and find Franky.
急いでフランキーを捜しましょう
You bastards...!
てめえら…
Hm?
ん？
Where's Robin?!
ロビンはどこだ～っ！
Luffy!
ルフィ！
Luffy?!
ルフィ！？
Nuisances...
邪魔を…
Robin! I've finally found you!
ロビン！やっと見つけたぞ！
Hey, Luffy! Where the hell have you been?!
おいルフィ！ てめえ一体どこにいやがったんだ！
Robin! I'm so glad to see you again!
ロビン！また会えてよかったぞ
Hold on a sec... What's going on here?
ちょっと待って この状況何？
Well, well...
やれやれ
Straw Hat...
麦わら
Paulie...
パウリー…
M-Mr. Iceburg...
ア…　アイスバーグさん
Wh-What the hell...
こ…　これは一体…
is going on?!
何がどうなってるんですか！
Paulie... Why... didn't you run?
パウリー てめえ　なぜ逃げねえ
What's going on here?!
何なんですか
This almost looks... like...
まるでこいつらが
they're the ones who've been trying to kill you!
あなたの命を狙った犯人みてえに…
You guys! What's with those get-ups?!
おめえら何で そんな格好してんだ！
Hey! Kalifa! Blueno! Kaku! Lucci!
おい！カリファ！ブルーノ！カク！ルッチ！
Stop jerking me around, you bastards!
冗談やめろてめえら！
Oh, yeah!
あっそうだ！
They're some of the shipwrights who were with you! Right?!
あいつら お前と一緒にいた船大工だ　なあ？
Oh, right... I've seen the guy with the long, square nose.
そういやあの四角っ鼻知ってるぞ
Then... the assassination was an inside job?!
まさか… 暗殺犯が内部にいたってこと？
What? What do you mean?!
えっ？どういうことだ？
Paulie, the truth is, we're government intelligence agents.
パウリー 実は俺たちは政府の諜報部員だ
Well, you'll forgive us if we apologize, right?
まっ　謝ったら許してくれるよな
We've been building ships together every day as colleagues.
共に日々船造りに明け暮れた仲間だ 俺たちは…
I know this is sudden, so if I step on Iceburg's face, would you believe me then?
突然で信じられねえなら アイスバーグの顔でも踏んでみせようか？
Stop messing around! That's enough...!
ふざけんな　もう十分だ
After all, you've got the same voice as that bull-masked man from earlier!
さっき聞いた牛仮面の声が おめえの声と一致するからな！
Dammit, you bastard! You can talk just fine!
ちくしょう…　てめえ… ちゃんとしゃべれんじゃねえかよ！
How dare you mock us?!
バカにしやがって！
Don't, Paulie!
やめろパウリー！
Pipe Hitch Knives!
パイプ･ヒッチ･ナイブス
Finger Pistol!
シガン
You still haven't learned your lesson, Paulie?
まだ懲りないのかパウリー
Hey, rope guy!
おい！ロープのヤツ！
Why...?
何で…
You guys...
おめえら…
Fighting back is pointless.
無駄に耐えるな
We've mastered techniques beyond the limits of human abilities.
俺たちは人間の限界を超える技を体得してる
After years of training, these techniques, the Six Powers, make human bodies as lethal as weapons.
長い訓練を重ね 人体を武器に匹敵させる武術“六式”
Gaining mastery of them gives one the strength of 100 people.
これを極めた１人の強度は 百人力に値する
Don't go overboard with the gambling.
大概にしろギャンブルばっかり
Jackass, I was lucky today! That's why I'm treating you guys!
バカ！今日はツイてたから おごってやってんだろ！
Blueno! More drinks!
ブルーノ！酒！酒！
Okay!
あいよ
Hey, Kalifa! You're dressed like that again?!
てめえ　カリファ！ またそんな格好を！
Stop it, Paulie. Just divert your gaze. Okay?
よさんか　パウリー 見なきゃよかろう　なあ？
What's wrong with you guys?
何で　お前らが…
Well, never mind.
まあいい
Unfortunately, my friend...
どのみち消す命
you're getting killed either way.
悲しいが友よ
Lucci, you...!
ルッチ貴様…
Stop it, you jerk!
やめろ！お前～っ！
Gum-Gum...
ゴムゴムの…
Iron Body.
テッカイ
...Gatling!
ガトリング～ッ！
What? It did nothing!
何だ？全然効かねえ
How annoying...
うっとうしい
Shave!
ソル
He disappeared!
消えた？
Finger Pistol!
シガン
Luffy!
ルフィ！
If you had a flesh-and-blood body, you'd be dead with a hole in your neck...
生身なら 首に風穴が開いて即死だったな
rubber man.
ゴム人間
What're you doing, Straw Hat?
何をしてる？麦わら
You're planning to kill him, aren't you?!
お前　こいつ殺す気だろ！
Didn't you guys all build ships together?!
一緒に船大工やってた 仲間じゃねえのかよ！
Until tonight, yes. But that's no longer the case.
さっきまでな　しかしもう違う
You guys have really turned your backs on them?!
本当に裏切り者か！
Fine, then!
じゃあいいよ
At the very least, I promised him...
とにかく俺はこいつと一緒に
that we'd beat the crap out of whoever was trying to kill Iceboss!
アイスのおっさんを殺そうとしているヤツらを ぶちのめそうと約束したんだ！
Why are you siding with Paulie?
なぜお前がパウリーに味方するんじゃ？
Because I've got business with you, too!
俺もお前らに用があるからだよ
Hey, Robin! Why are you with these jerks?!
おいロビン！ 何でおめえがこんなヤツらと一緒にいるんだ！
If you wanna leave the crew, tell us why!
出ていきたきゃ ちゃんと理由を言え！
He's right! They said they work for the government! So why?!
そうよ！こいつら政府の人間だっていうじゃない！ どうして…
You people don't listen well, do you?
聞き分けが悪いのね
I already said my goodbyes to the cook and the doctor.
コックさんと船医さんにお別れは言ったはずよ
You didn't tell them?
伝えてくれなかったの？
I did! But I can't accept it, either! Why, Robin?!
伝えたよ！だけど俺だって納得できねえ 何でだ ロビン！
To make my wish come true...
私の願いをかなえるためよ
A wish that can never come true if I stay with you!
あなたたちと一緒にいても 決してかなわない願いを！
In order to achieve it, I'll make any sacrifice!
それを成し遂げるためならば 私はどんな犠牲もいとわない！
So then... framing your friends for murder didn't even get a second thought?
それで　平気で仲間を 暗殺犯に仕立て上げたのか
What's this wish of yours?!
願いってのは何だ！
I don't need to tell you.
話す必要がないわ
This is insane!
正気の沙汰じゃねえ
Because she's...!
その女は…
Have you lost it, Nico Robin?!
気は確かかニコ･ロビン
Do you realize what you're about to do?!
お前は自分が何をやろうとしてるのか 分かってるのか！
You no longer have the right to lecture me about anything!
あなたにはもう 何も言う権利はないはずよ
Keep your mouth shut!
黙っていなさい！
Mr. Iceburg!
アイスバーグさん！
I won't let anyone get in my way!
誰にも邪魔はさせない！
Hey, Robin! What're you doing?!
おいロビン！何やってんだ
Are you being serious?!
お前本気かよ！
Robin! What happened to you?!
ロビン！どうしちゃったんだ！
Are you really our enemy now?! Robin!
本当にもう敵なのか？ロビン！
Sorry, but I'm going to have to cut this short.
悪いが そこまでにしてもらおう
There's an important person we need to find right away, so we're in a hurry.
我々はこれから重要人物を 捜さなきゃならないんだ　急いでいる
We no longer have any business here...
この屋敷にももう用はないし
nor do we have business with any of you.
君らにももう完全に用がない
Kalifa, how much time is left?
カリファ　あとどれくらいだ？
Two minutes.
２分よ
Pardon our abruptness, but this building will go up in flames in two minutes.
突然だが　あと２分で この屋敷は炎に包まれることになっている
What?
ええっ！？
– What?!
–　ええっ！？
What'd you say?!
何だと？
Fire is an effective tool for destroying all sorts of evidence.
いろいろな証拠を消すのに 炎は有効な手段だ
If you don't want to burn to death, you should leave the building immediately.
君たちも焼け死にたくなければ 速やかに屋敷を出ることだ
Well, of course...
まっもちろん…
that's assuming you even can.
それができればの話だが
Looks like they're planning on killing us.
どうやら俺たちを消す気らしいな
Also, I think it's clear whose side Nico Robin has chosen.
ニコ･ロビンも向こうにいたいようだが…
Luffy, do you accept that Robin has left the ship?
ルフィ お前ロビンの下船にゃ納得できたのか？
Not like this!
できるかーっ！
Shouting isn't necessary.
そうほえるな
Soon, several rooms on the first floor will burst into flames.
じきに１階のいくつかの部屋から火の手が上がる
Oh well, it must've been caused by pirates.
まっ　犯人は海賊なんだ
That's how these things play out.
そんなこともあるだろう
You bastards...!
お前ら…
Doing what you want while pinning it on someone else...!
人の仮面をかぶって好き放題なんて
That's just bad taste!
趣味悪いわね！
You guys are already criminals. No harm done.
もともと汚れた仮面に不都合もなかろう
Well, then...
じゃあ…
I'll go on ahead.
私は先に行くわ
Right. You did your part. Much appreciated.
ああ　役目は果たした ご苦労
Wait, Robin!
待て！ロビン！
I won't allow it!
認めねえぞ！
Goodbye.
さようなら
– Robin!
–　ロビン！
Do not...
行かせるな
let Nico Robin go.
ニコ･ロビンを
Where're you going this time... when we'd finally found you?!
またどこ行くんだよ！ やっと見つけたのに！
Outta my way, you bastard!
どけお前！
Iron Body.
テッカイ
Why are their bodies so hard?!
何でこいつらこんなに体硬えんだ！
Our bodies are well trained.
鍛え上げられた我らの肉体は
We can raise their solidity to that of iron.
鉄の甲殻にまで硬度を高められる
However, that's not to say defense is all we have.
しかし　受けるばかりが能じゃなく…
I said outta my way!
どけって言ってんだ～っ！
Paper Art.
カミエ
He's dodging every punch... and he's a big guy!
全然当たらねえ あんなでかいのに！
He's fluttering like paper!
まるで紙みたいにヒラヒラと…
Robin!
ロビン！
Wait!
待て！
You son of a...!
このっ…
Gum-Gum...
ゴムゴムの…
Pistol!
ピストル！
Shave!
ソル！
He disappeared too!
また消えた！
When your legs are so tremendously strong to give the illusion of vanishing...
消えたように見えるほどの 爆発的な脚力があれば…
You bastard!
にゃろ！
Moon Walk.
ゲッポウ
...you'll also be able to kick the air and float.
空を蹴り浮くことさえできる
He's flying! What the...?!
飛んでる！何だ！？
– There's also...
–　さらに
– ...Tempest Kick.
–　ランキャク
A slashing attack...?!
斬撃か！？
You two...!
お前ら
Duck!
伏せろ！
Why?!
何で？
Luffy!
ルフィ！
Did their kicks really just cut the wall?!
蹴りで壁が斬れたの？今…
It's possible by kicking fast enough to create a sharp gust.
鎌風を呼び起こす速度があれば可能
That's a tempest kick.
それがランキャク
We met on your ship, didn't we, Roronoa?
船で会うたな　ロロノア
This means you aren't a real shipwright, huh?
お前船大工じゃなかったんだな
So then, when you assessed our ship, was that...?
じゃあまさかあの時の船の査定…
Unfortunately for you, I assessed that ship seriously.
残念ながら 船の査定は真面目にやった
That is unfortunate!
そりゃ残念だ！
– Luffy!
–　ルフィ
Don't go, Robin!
行くな！ロビン！
I still need to talk to you!
まだ話は終わってねえ！
No. We're through. You'll never see me again.
いいえ　終わりよ もう二度と会うことはない
Robin!
ロビン！
Luffy! Hurry up and catch Robin!
ルフィ！ 早くロビンを取っ捕まえろ！
Roronoa, you must be pretty confident to take your eyes off of me.
ロロノア よそ見をするとは余裕じゃのう
Ah! Zoro!
あっ！ゾロ～！
Finger Pistol.
シガン
We don't need bullets to puncture the human body.
人体を撃ち抜くのに弾丸などいらん
You... bastard...! Let me go!
こ…　の…　野郎！離せ！
He captured Luffy so easily!
ルフィが簡単に捕まった
Go, Nico Robin.
行け　ニコ･ロビン
– Robin!
–　ロビン！
Dammit...
クソッ
Luffy!
ルフィ！
Zoro!
ゾロ！
How can they be that strong?
何なの　あいつらの強さ…
What are you people?
何者なんだてめえら…
We come from different worlds.
環境が違う
For as long as we, the members of CP9, can remember,
我々ＣＰ９は物心ついた頃より
we've been prepped to risk our lives for the government...
政府のために命を使う覚悟と
and have trained to surpass the limits of human abilities.
人体の限界を超えるための訓練を受けてきた
As a result, we've mastered the superhuman techniques of the Six Powers.
そして得た力が ６つの超人的体技　六式
By now, I'm sure you fully understand
よく身にしみたはずだ
that we four, who've been entrusted with the World Government's vital tasks,
世界政府の重要任務を任される我々４人と
are in a completely different league than you lowly pirates!
たかだか一海賊団のお前たちとの 桁違いの戦闘力の差が
This is a world-class top secret.
この一件は世界的機密事項
Something like this does not concern the likes of you.
お前たちごときが 手を触れていいヤマではない
Lucci...
ルッチ
The igniters are about to go off. We have to hurry, too.
発火装置作動の時間よ 私たちも急がなくては
Yeah.
ああ
But this is a rare occasion.
だがせっかくだ最後に
I'll show you something neat before we go.
面白いものを見せようか
A devil fruit!
悪魔の実！
Which one?!
何の実だ
Lucci... You...!
ルッチ　てめえ…
The Cat-Cat Fruit:
ネコネコの実
Leopard.
モデル“レオパルド”
A leopard human...
ヒョウ人間か…
H-He's huge!
で…　でけえ！
Why do you look like that?!
何だ　その姿は…
What the hell are you?!
何なんだよ！